https://www.bisongear.com/privacy

3850 Ohio Ave  •  St Charles IL 60174  •  1-800-AT-BISON  •  +1-630-377-4327
All Products
Integral Horsepower ProductsAC Parallel Shaft GearmotorsDC Parallel Shaft GearmotorsHollow Shaft Offset GearmotorsInverter Duty AC GearmotorsRight Angle GearmotorsPMDC MotorsWashdownReducersDrivesAccessories
Industries Ag & ConstructionEnergyFood & Beverage Food & Beverage PackagingIndustrial MachineryMotion ControlMedicalTransportationCapabilities The Bison AdvantageCustom EngineeringMade in AmericaLean ManufacturingResources Case StudiesVideos3D CAD ConfiguratorReturn PolicyPrivacy PolicyGlossary of TermsLiteratureTerms and ConditionsAdvertisementsFAQsCompetitor Cross ReferenceTorque TalkAbout WelcomeHistoryMissionBisonCaresAffiliationsContact Us EmploymentCustomer SupportContact Information
Privacy Policy
Bison Privacy Policy
Bison takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy governs and details the main privacy principles we apply to the data we collect through our website www.bisongear.com.
Data collection and use of personally identifiable information
We collect personally identifiable information, such as your name and email address, directly from you when you complete the "Contact Us" form on our website.
We use this information to respond to the demand you have submitted to us through the Contact form.
We also use this information for marketing purposes, such as to send you our newsletter or other promotional emails. You may choose to stop receiving our marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these communications.
We do not share this information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We may share your information with our subsidiaries, affiliated companies, trusted third parties working under instruction for Bison, such as an email service provider, or with data centers, exclusively for storage purpose.
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, as part of a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.
You may update, access or delete your personally identifiable information by contacting us at zolson@bisongear.com . We will respond to your request within thirty days.
Our site includes links to other websites whose privacy practices may differ from ours. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any website you visit.
Data security and retention
The security of your information is fundamental to Bison. We have implemented industry standard security measures, which include the use of firewalls and encryption. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure.
Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide our services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.
Bison commitments
Bison collects and uses data in accordance with all applicable laws and regulations, including but not limited to laws governing privacy and data protection.
Changes to our privacy policy
Please note that we may update or change this privacy policy. If we revise our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we make any material changes we will notify you by means of a notice on this site prior to the change becoming effective. Please check the Bison website at www.bisongear.com for the latest version of the privacy policy.
Effective Date: 3/10/2016
Product Quick Search
Motor TypeAC ParallelAC Right AngleDC MotorsDC ParallelDC Right AngleGear ReducersTorque (in-lbs)0 - 100100 - 250250 - 500500+RPM0 - 5051 - 150151 - 500500+Horsepower0 - 1/101/10 - 1/41/4 - 1/21/2 - 1Gear Ratio0 - 5050 - 100100 - 10001000+ Search
advanced search
Product Cross Reference
Torque Talk
8.25.20
BisonCares Cancels 2020 Charitable Golf Outing
7.24.20
Powering Conveyor Systems Across the Country
3.23.20
COVID-19 Update
10.10.18
A Solution for Powering Food & Beverage Packaging Lines
More
Product Search
1-800-AT-BISON+1-630-377-4327
IndustriesAg & ConstructionEnergyFood & BeverageFood & Beverage PackagingIndustrial MachineryMotion ControlMedicalTransportationCapabilitiesThe Bison AdvantageCustom EngineeringMade in AmericaLean ManufacturingResourcesCase StudiesVideos3D CAD ConfiguratorReturn PolicyPrivacy PolicyGlossary of TermsLiteratureTerms and ConditionsAdvertisementsFAQsCompetitor Cross ReferenceAboutWelcomeHistoryMissionBisonCaresAffiliationsContact UsEmploymentCustomer SupportContact Information
